Dimitri Nakos

2340 Greenland Ave. Charlotte, NC 28208

704-904-9661 <u>dimi1nakos@gmail.com</u>

Summary

Highly-motivated to learn new technologies and work on a new career path for myself. Started in the automotive industry 8 years ago and developed problem solving skills, time management, led teams and have trained new hires. Learning HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.

Professional Experience

♦ Automotive Technician, Keffer Volkswagen

December 2017 – Present

Troubleshoot and problem solve issues with emerging automotive technologies.

Utilize web based training and information.

Coordinated group brainstorming for difficult diagnosis.

Trained new technicians starting out in the field.

Performed accurate and timely diagnosis and repairs.

♦ Automotive Technician, South Charlotte Hyundai

August 2016 – December 2017

Performed detail oriented inspections.

Inspected every brand new vehicle with emphasis on detail.

Mediated between the customers and service writers.

Supervised and assigned tasks to technicians.

♦ Automotive Technician, Carolina Volkswagen

January 2011 – August 2017

Started from no experience to become one of the top technicians in the service department within a year. Delegated tasks to technicians.

Informed customers of services provided and necessary tasks required.

Started as a Customer Service Adviser organized and communicated information for customers.

Education

♦ University of North Carolina at Charlotte

Associates of the Arts, History

Skills

Problem Solving Time Management Team Leader
Computer Skills Detail Oriented Studied UI/UX
Studying JavaScript Studying HTML/CSS Customer Service

References

◆ Davis Sithideth 846-316-5554

NASCAR Web Development Team

◆ Brian Mover 704-488-0915

Keffer Volkswagen, Service manager

▶ Ronnie Taylor 704-604-9446

Keffer Volkswagen, Master Technician